{
    "id": "5986e09094cc4a70aeb5f9a9cd08df66",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Drop And Draw",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I dropped ............................. my aunt's house yesterday.",
            "description": "To drop round is to visit without making an arrangement. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "round"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b484137f49164d1dabd3504b48d59107"
        },
        {
            "question": "The demand for digital cameras has dropped ............................",
            "description": "It demand drops off, it becomes less.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9aec5fa2721949c9b8f1cbfab5beb1db"
        },
        {
            "question": "I dropped ..................................... in the middle of the show.",
            "description": "To drop off is to begin to sleep.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4fe1aa7fbffe494e858fad8c8a126a14"
        },
        {
            "question": "Profits dropped ................................. during the last quarter.",
            "description": "Drop off can mean become less.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "back",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "608e6bb741d64a61ab7c80820b9d3f61"
        },
        {
            "question": "Get in. I will drop you ............................... at college.",
            "description": "To drop somebody off is to take them to a place.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7470823d4e174963b34aeaf920a31a15"
        },
        {
            "question": "Aunt Martha would often drop .......................................... on us.",
            "description": "To drop in on somebody is to visit them informally.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22f7553062934316a93e8cdcbb5ec112"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can drop .................................... whenever you want.",
            "description": "To drop over is to visit casually.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "98bcea2817aa4a569119a43f98b3eebf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nights draw ...................................... fast in winter.",
            "description": "When nights draw in they start earlier.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "23090883e22e49ab8862b4539d7ed458"
        },
        {
            "question": "He drew ................................. the lecture unnecessarily.",
            "description": "To draw out a lecture is to make it longer.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db45c0756030490296a98da4c9e0e1fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Drivers are required to draw .................................. at the lights.",
            "description": "To draw up is to halt.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a4208e01d3a4b338fc286b020d1596b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't want to get drawn ......................................... this scandal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "into",
                "onto"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd6c0d4e71d94737bc26b4fc77386a44"
        },
        {
            "question": "The protestors drew .................................. when the police approached them.",
            "description": "To draw back is to move away.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "back"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f3951979d2e340b69732fcd76d090fb0"
        }
    ]
}